#### **RESUME**

Name : MURUGAN .K

Qualification : BE(INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY)

Email id :murugankaliyankvm@gmail.com

Mobile No : (+91) 9787105550

Address: No 26, Krishna Nagar, Pammel, Chennai 600043

#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:**

**4 + years of Industry experience in providing User Experience Design & Front End Development and**Development with most usable enterprise wide applications. Specialized in full web site development, Front End Development React Js and JavaScript and Development.

# **WORKING EXPERIENCE:**

- Currently working as a Front End Developer in AppsDocker, Chennai from Apr 2021 to till date.
- Worked as a Front End Developer in Koncepts, Chennai from June 2018 to March 2021.
- Worked as a Web Developer in Os InfoTech, Bangalore fromMarch 2013 to September 2015.

### **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION:**

- Bachelor of Engineering in Information Technology in April 2012 from Annamalai University, Chidambaram with First Class.
- Passed HSC in March 2008 from G.H.S. School, Thiyagadurgam with 69.83%.
- Passed SSLC in March 2006 from G.H.S. School, Asanur with 70.60%.

## **SKILLS:**

HTML5, CSS3, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, BOOTSTRAP (Beginner level ), REACT JS, (Beginner) Node Js, Express js (Beginner)

Script Editor: Vs Code

**Graphics Tools: Photoshop** 

Project #1:

www.bharatmatchpoint.com

Bharatmatchpoint is an matrimonial community, Tested stability for over 20 different websites.

#### Technology used:

Front end

Html5 and Css3

• JavaScript Functionality Development

## Framework:

React Js

#### Back End:

- Node is
- Express Js
- Rest Api

#### Database:

MySql

#### Project #2:

### Dynamixs - www.sixsigma.com

It also enables administrators to analyses data to measure learning outcomes of candidate and students within their job.

# Technology used:

Front end

Html5 and Css3 JavaScript Functionality Development

#### Framework:

React Js

#### **Back End:**

Node js Express Js

# Database:

MySql

### Project #3:

# **Online Rummy Application**

**Rummy** is a matching-card game, also called a draw and discard game, which involves melding cards into sets and sequences. It features several challenging

## Technology used:

Front end

Html5 and Css3 JavaScript Functionality Development

#### Framework:

React Js

# Back End:

Node js Express Js

#### **Database:**

MongosDB

# **HOBBIES:**

- Reading Books
- Hearing Music

#### **Personal Details:**

Gender	:	Male
Marital Status	:	Single
Father's Name	:	C.Kaliyan
Permanent Address	:	No: 2/30,Mariyamman koivil ST
		Kallakurichi (TK & DT)
		Tamil Nadu. 606 305
Languages Known	:	English, Tamil
I hereby declare that the above written particulars are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.		
Place:		
Date:		( MURUGAN .K )

: 32 years, 11-04-1990

Age & DOB